My name's Conan Edogawa!
اسمي إيدوغاوا كونان
High school student Shinichi was forced to take a drug that shrunk him.
أُجبر طالب الثانوية كودو شينتشي على تجرّع عقار قلص جسده
Although smaller, my mind remains that of a sharp detective!
،رغم أنّي أصبحت أصغر !لا يزال عقلي عقل متحرٍّ عظيم
Today's case involves a missing corpse!
!تتضمن قضيّة اليوم جثّةً مفقودة
Even if you do deceive everybody, there's still always only one truth!
!حتى لو خدعتَ الجميع، تبقى الحقيقة واحدة دوماً
Sure is quiet around here lately...
الهدوء يعمّ هنا مؤخراً
The Junior Detective League can't do anything if nobody needs help...
لا يمكن لفرقة فتيان التحرّي فعل شيء دون تلقي طلب مساعدة
Of course not.
بالطبع
If clients showed up that easily, we detectives would be worry-free.
،لو كان العُملاء يظهرون بهذه السهولة لما عانينا نحن المحققون أيّ قلق
And Professor Agasa went through the trouble of making badges for us...
...صنع لنا البروفسور آغاسا تلك الشارات أيضاً
They look cool no matter how many times I look at them!
!تبدو رائعةً مهما نظرتُ لها
Detective Boys... The Junior Detective League's exclusive design!
فتيان التحرّي، تصميم فرقة فتيان التحرّي الحصري
They even act as transceivers!
!تتمتّع بوظيفة إرسال واستقبال أيضاً
Bah! These badges are worthless if we have no cases to solve--
!لا قيمة لهذه الشارات دون قضايا لنحلّها
Excuse me...
المعذرة
You're Hiroki, from the next classroom over!
!أنت هيروكي من الفصل المجاور
What is it? A murder?!
!ما الأمر؟ جريمة قتل؟
Fraud?!
!احتيال؟
Your parents are having an affair?!
!خيانة زوجية بين والديك؟
No... Akira disappeared last night...
كـ-كلا، اختفى أكيرا ليلة البارحة
A missing persons case!
!قضيّة شخص مفقود
Kidnapping isn't out of the question!
الاختطاف ليس مستبعداً
So what does she look like?!
كيف مظهره إذاً؟
I have a picture of her. Here.
لديّ صورة، هاكم
A cat?!
!قطّة؟
Are you saying it was this cat that disappeared?
أتقصد أنّ هذه القطّة هي من فقدته؟
Yes.
أجل
Too bad it wasn't a kidnapping!
!لم يكن اختطافاً للأسف
I can pay you each 10 yen.
يمكنني أن أدفع لكم 10 ينّ لكل فرد
10 yen?!
!عشرة ينّات؟
No way! We only handle higher-level cases!
كلا، نحن نستقبل القضايا رفيعة المستوى فقط
I'm sure the cat will come back eventually!
ستعود القطّة إن انتظرت بالتأكيد
But...
...لـ-لكن
Bye now.
إلى اللقاء
I was going to give you some Masked Yaiba cards if you found her...
كنتُ سأعطيكم بعض بطاقات يايبا المقنّع إن وجدتموها
See! I collect them!
انظروا، أنا أجمعها
Masked Yaiba cards?!
!بـ-بطاقات يايبا المقنّع؟
What's more, these are the super rare...
...كما أنّها البطاقات شديدة الندرة
...Hyper Golden Cards!
!الذهبية الفائقة
We accept the case!
!نقبل القضيّة
What's with you guys?!
ما خطبكم؟
Darn it, we can't find her anywhere...
تبّاً، لا نستطيع إيجادها في أيّ مكان
That's strange... She disappeared yesterday, so she should still be nearby...
غريب، اختفت بالأمس لذا يُفترض أنّها لا تزال في القرب
Hey. We worked really hard, so give us our cards now.
أنت، بذلنا جهداً كبيراً لذا يُفترض أن تعطينا البطاقات الآن
No way. You didn't find her.
كلا، لم تجدوها
Say, does this cat have any habits or special abilities or anything?
أخبرني، ألتلك القطة عادات أو مميزات ما؟
Now that you mention it, Akira's meow is a lot different than other cats'.
حسناً، مواء أكيرا مختلف عن بقية القطط
Like this...
...هكذا
Yes! Just like that!
أجل، كذاك
Where did it come from?!
!من أين أتى؟
From that house!
!من ذاك المنزل
Akira! Akira!
!أكيرا! أكيرا
Akira!
!أكيرا
We did it!
!وجدناها
She's covered in blood!
!تغطيها الدماء
We have to help her right away!
!علينا مساعدتها فوراً
No! This cat is uninjured!
كلا، لا جراح بهذه القطّة
Which means...
...مما يعني
It couldn't be!
...أيمكن
Wait for us, Conan! What's going on?!
!انتظر يا كونان! ما الخطب؟
Is there something there?
أيوجد شيء هناك؟
Let me see too!
!دعني أرى أيضاً
Me too!
!وأنا
I have to call the police right away!
!الشرطة... عليّ الاتصال بهم فوراً
Are you the ones who made the call?
أأنتم من أجرى الاتصال؟
Did you really see a corpse?
أرأيتم جثّةً حقاً؟
Yes!
!أجل
Honest!
!صدقاً
There's no question about it, Inspector.
لا شكّ في الأمر سيّدي المفتش
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
Plus, nobody has left the house since we discovered the body.
كما أنّه لم يغادر أحدٌ المنزل مذ اكتشفنا الجثة
In other words, the corpse is still inside!
مما يعني أنّ الجثة لا تزال داخله
Police! Open up!
!نحن الشرطة! افتح الباب
What's the racket?!
!ما هذه الجلبة؟
These kids say they saw a dead body in your house.
يقول هؤلاء الصغار أنّهم رأوا جثّةً في منزلك
A dead body?!
!جثّة؟
We're certain we saw it!
!رأيناها بلا شك
A man in the bathroom!
!رجل في الحمّام
He was lying in the bathtub, covered in blood!
!كان ملقياً وتغطيه الدماء
Ridiculous! I was just taking a bath!
سخافة، كنتُ أستحم لتويّ
See for yourself! It's that room straight ahead!
إنّها تلك الغرفة أمامكم مباشرةً
I think I'll do just that.
سألقي نظرة قليلاً
Hey!
!لـ-لحظة
It's gone! The body is gone!
...ليست هنا! الجثّة
It disappeared!
اختفت
That's impossible!
مستحيل
See! No corpses! These brats are probably just pulling a prank on you!
رأيتم؟ لا جثث هنا! كان مقلباً !من هؤلاء الأطفال بالتأكيد
But we really saw it!
!لكننا رأيناها صدقاً
There was a dead body, covered in blood and lying in the bathroom!
!جثّة تغطيها الدماء طريحة في الحمّام
Yeah!
!أجل
This guy must've hidden it!
!لا بد أنّ هذا الرجل أخفاها
What?!
!ما-ما الذي تقوله؟
Approximately 15 minutes have passed from the time you called us
مضت 15 دقيقة تقريباً مذ اتّصالكم بنا
until we arrived here.
حتى وصولنا هنا
That's more than enough time to hide a body.
إنّه وقتٌ كافٍ لإخفاء جثّة
This is ridiculous!
سخافة
Search all you want! I'm going upstairs to sleep!
ابحثوا قدرما تشاؤون! سأصعد للأعلى لأنام
You don't mind if we search without you then?
لا تمانع إن بحثنا دون حضورك إذاً؟
Fine by me!
لا أهتم
Ransack the place if you want, there's nothing to find!
قلّبوا المكان إن شئتم، لن تجدوا شيئاً مريباً
If you have any problems, tell my brother. He'll be home soon!
،إن كانت هناك مشاكل فأخبروا أخي سيعود للمنزل قريباً
But the police must be bored to death
لكن لا بدّ أنّ الشرطة غارقة في الضجر
if they'll make a fuss over a bunch of deviant little miscreants!
لتثير جلبةً حول مقالب أطفال مشاغبين
Bah!
تبّاً
Search! The body's here somewhere!
!ابحثوا! لا بدّ أن الجثة في مكانٍ ما
Search every nook and cranny!
!اقلبوا البيت رأساً على عقب
Find the body at all costs!
!جدوا الجثّة مهما كلّف الأمر
Um...
المعذرة
Did something happen here?
أحصل شيءٌ ما هنا؟
Inspector!
حضرة المفتش
The younger brother has returned.
رجع الأخ الأصغر
W-What is this...? What's going on?!
!ما-ما هذا؟ ما الذي يجري؟
This lad here says he saw a corpse in your house.
قال هذا الفتى أنّه رأى جثةً في منزلكم
A corpse?!
جثّة؟
Whoops!
!تبّاً
What are you doing?!
!ما-ما الذي تفعله؟
No, that's alright! It wasn't worth much...
...لا مشكلة، لم تكن مرتفعة القيمة
Hey! Keep it down, will you?!
!أنتم! اخرسوا! ألا يمكنكم التزام الهدوء؟
I take it my brother is upstairs?
هل أخي كازيوشي في الأعلى؟
Yes. He seems rather angry, too.
أجل، يبدو أنّه غاضب أيضاً
Pardon my rudeness, but what exactly does your brother do for a living?
المعذرة، لكن ما عمل أخيك بالضبط؟
He's a writer, for the time being.
إنّه كاتبٌ للوقت الراهن
But in reality, he usually stays at home and does nothing at all...
لكنّه في الواقع يمكث في البيت عادةً ...ولا يقوم بشيء
Here's my card...
هذه بطاقتي
Tanaka Tomofumi...
تاناكا توموفومي
I see you work for a securities firm...
تعمل في شركة أوراق مالية
So just you and your brother live here?
أأنت وأخوك وحدكما من يعيش هنا؟
That's right.
أجل
Though technically it's my house. My brother lives here for free.
رغم أنّه منزلي فعلياً، يعيش أخي بلا مقابل
What's this?
ما هذا؟
A leaf?
ورقة؟
Well, we've checked the house from top to bottom...
...بحثنا في المنزل من سقفه لأسفله
All that's left is your brother's room.
بقيت غرفة أخيك فقط
Yes. I hope he doesn't get too mad at you...
حسناً، آمل ألا يغضب كثيراً
Brother...?
أخي؟
...the high pressure ridge will bring clear skies to most of Japan.
سيجلب النتوء الجبلي مرتفع الضغط ...سماءً صافية لمعظم أرجاء اليابان
It's alright. It looks like he's asleep.
لا بأس، يبدو أنّه نائم
I see.
هكذا إذاً
...showers starting at around 1 o'clock.
تبدأ زخّات المطر قرابة الواحدة ظهراً
The rain may remain heavy until evening.
قد يستمر هطول المطر الغزير حتّى المساء
What can you tell me about it?
ما أمرها؟
Tanaka-san?
تاناكا-سان؟
Come on! If you're going to sleep, at least turn the TV off!
!يا إلهي، أطفئ التلفاز على الأقل إن كنت ستنام
It sounds like he heard me...
يبدو أنّه سمعني
I believe I've shown you everything I can...
أعتقد أنّكم رأيتم كلّ شيء الآن
And no dead bodies whatsoever...
ولا وجود لأيّ جثّة
You little scoundrels!
!أيّها الأشقياء
We're not lying!
!نحن لا نكذب
Say, the body could've been carried outside by now!
يمكن أن الجثّة نُقلت للخارج سلفاً
But Conan-kun...
...لكن يا كونان-كن
Didn't you say no one entered or left this house before we arrived?
ألم تقل أنّه لم يغادر أحد المنزل قبل وصولنا؟
That's what I said,
قلتُ ذلك
but I only watched from the phone booth in front of the house.
لكنّي كنت أراقب مقدمة المنزل من حجرة الهاتف فقط
I didn't see the backyard.
لم أرَ الفناء الخلفي
But there's a high wall behind the house.
لكن يوجد حائط مرتفع خلف هذا المنزل
But you saw that big tree, right?
رأيت الشجرة الكبيرة مع ذلك، صحيح؟
If you tied a body to yourself and used that tree,
إن ربطت جثّةً بجسمك واستعملت تلك الشجرة
you could get over the wall!
سيمكنك تجاوز الحائط
Tanaka residence!
منزل تاناكا
Yes?
أجل؟
No, you must have the wrong number.
كلا، لا بد أنّه الرقم الخطأ
That's okay!
لا مشكلة
Goodbye!
وداعاً
Wrong number. So what were we talking about again?
كان اتصالاً خاطئاً، عمَّ كنا نتحدث؟
The tree in the back.
الشجرة في الخلف
Ah, that was originally there when I bought the place.
كانت موجودةً عندما اشتريتُ المنزل
Was the ringer off on that phone?!
هل كان رنين ذاك الهاتف لا يعمل؟
Hey! Are you alright up there?!
أأنت بخيرٍ هناك؟
Y-Yes, sir!
!أجل
Can you climb over it with someone tied to you?
أيمكن تسلّقها وشخص مربوطٌ بك؟
I think I can...
...أظن بإمكاني
I can't, Inspector!
لا جدوى حضرة المفتش
I can't get down. The outer side of the wall is an embankment!
لا يمكنني النزول، الجانب الخارجي للحائط سدٌّ مائي
Are there any footholds or anything of the sort?
ألا يوجد موضع أقدام أو ما شابه؟
There's a walkway about 40 centimeters wide,
هناك مسار بعرض 40 سنتيمتر تقريباً
but it would be impossible to use with a body tied to me!
لكن من المستحيل سلوكه وأنا أحمل جثّة
Even if I could get down, it would take everything I had just to walk.
حتّى لو تمكنت من النزول، سأحتاج كلّ جهدي لمجرد المشي
There's no corpse inside the house,
،لا جثّة داخل المنزل
and it's impossible to carry one outside!
ومن المستحيل نقل واحدة للخارج
In other words, you lied.
مما يعني أنّكم كذبتم
You can't be serious!?
...لا يمكن
Let's go, everyone!
!لنغادر جميعاً
Wait, Inspector!
!انتظر سيّدي المفتش
We really saw it!
...رأينا حقاً
Even if you did catch that gang of Italian thieves,
،حتّى لو أمسكتم بعصابة اللّصوص الإيطالية تلك
it was still stupid of me to trust you!
كانت حماقة منّي أن أثق بكم
How?
كيف؟
How could the body have vanished?
كيف اختفت الجثّة؟
All I can think of at this point is that the older brother washed the blood off
كلّ ما يسعني التفكير به الآن أنّ الأخ الأكبر غسل الدم
while the younger brother made preparations to carry the body out.
بينما تكفل الأصغر بتجهيزات نقل الجثة للخارج
It's just like the leaf that was on the younger brother...
إنّها كالورقة التي كانت على الأخ الأصغر
Does this mean that they really did use this tree to get the body outside?
أي أنّه استعمل هذه الشجرة لنقل الجثة للخارج فعلاً
Hey there!
!مرحباً
What're you doing here? Are you stupid?!
!أغبياء! ما الذي تفعلونه؟
You idiot!
!غبيّ
We can't let them call our detective club a bunch of liars!
لا يمكننا تركهم ينعتوننا نحن !فرقة فتيان التحرّي بالكاذبين
These guys can be such a pain...
...هؤلاء الفتيان
Oh no! Hide!
!كلا! اختبئوا
Did they see us?
هل رأونا؟
That scary man's still sleeping there!
لا يزال ذاك الرجل المخيف نائماً هنا
Now what do we do?
...مشكلة
Jeez, he should at least close the curtain or something...
تباً، كان عليه إغلاق الستائر على الأقل
And doesn't he ever get tired sleeping like that?!
وألا يشعر بالإرهاق وهو ينام بذاك الشكل؟
Wait a second!
!لحظة
Have I been looking at this the wrong way the whole time?!
!هل كنت أسيئ الفهم من البداية؟
Conan-kun!
!كونان-كن
What's going on?!
!ما-ما الخطب؟
I might've figured out the trick the killer used to hide the body!
لعلّي اكتشفت الحيلة التي استعملها المجرم لإخفاء الجثة
Wait here. I'm going inside to see if I'm right.
انتظروا، سأدخل للتحقق من ذلك
Okay! We'll help too!
!حسنٌ، سنساعدك أيضاً
No! There may be a killer inside!
كلا!، قد يكون هناك قاتل في الداخل
You guys go wait by the phone booth outside!
انتظروا عند حجرة الهاتف خارجاً
I'll contact you if I find the body!
سأتصل بكم إن وجدتُ الجثة
If I do, it's your job to contact the police right away!
واتّصلوا بالشرطة فوراً عندها
He locked it!
!أقفلها
Now for the room upstairs!
!عليّ التوجه للغرفة في الأعلى
This isn't good--he's still awake!
تبّاً، لا يزال مستيقظاً
What did he put down?!
ما الذي وضعه؟
A cell phone...
...هاتف خلوي
That's it! That trick could work if you used this!
!هكذا إذاً! ستنجح الحيلة إن استعملت هذا
I've got most of this case figured out now!
بدأت تتّضح لي هذه القضية
Conan sure is taking a long time...
تأخّر كونان
Yeah...
أجل
He said he'd contact us using these miniature transceivers
قال أنّه سيتصل بنا عبر أجهزة الإرسال المصغرة هذه
if he found the body...
...إن وجد الجثة
What if he's actually trying to take all the credit for himself?!
أيمكن أنّه يحاول الاستحواذ على الثناء لنفسه؟
Conan-kun would never do something like that!
!لن يفعل كونان-كن شيئاً كذاك أبداً
This is the room!
!هذه هي
I see! So I was right!
!هكذا إذاً! كنتُ محقاً
There's an answering machine and a VCR in this room!
توجد آلة ردّ آلي وجهاز تسجيل فيديو في هذه الغرفة
Uh oh!
!تباً
That's odd...
...غريب
I thought I heard something in here. Must've been my imagination...
،ظننتُ أنّي سمعت شيئاً هنا ...لكن لعلّها كانت مخيلتي
Hey, what's taking so long, Conan? What're you doing?!
!تأخرّت يا كونان! ما الذي تفعله؟
Who's there?!
!من هناك؟
Oh no!
!تـ-تباً
It sounds like he's been spotted!
!يبدو أنّه وجده
Get out of there, Conan-kun!
!اهرب يا كونان-كن
There's no use in hiding!
!لا جدوى من الاختباء
Give yourself up and come out!
!استسلم واخرج
Dammit! I guess I have no choice now but to leave my transmitter on!
اللعنة، لا خيار لديّ الآن سوى ترك جهاز الإرسال يعمل
You're the one who should give yourself up, Tanaka-san!
أنت من عليه الاستسلام يا تاناكا-سان
Neither we nor the police could find the corpse...
لم نجد لا نحن ولا الشرطة الجثّة
But it was in the house the entire time, right under our noses, even!
لكنّها كانت في المنزل طوال الوقت وأمام أنظارنا
That's right.
صحيح
The corpse I'm referring to is the man who was sitting in this very room,
الجثّة التي أشير لها هي هذا الرجل الذي كان جالساً في هذه الغرفة
watching television...
...ويشاهد التلفاز
Your older brother!
!أخوك الأكبر
Who are you?!
!من أنت؟
Conan Edogawa. A detective.
إيدوغاوا كونان، مُتحرٍّ
A detective?!
مُتحرٍّ؟
This is how your trick worked...
...هكذا كانت الحيلة التي وضعتها
Seeing that we had discovered your brother's body,
،بعدما ضبطتنا نكتشف جثّة أخيك
you washed all the blood off him in the bathroom,
غسلت الدمّ عنه في الحمام
put a bathrobe on him, sat him in a chair upstairs,
وألبسته ثوب استحمام وأجلسته منتصباً على كرسيّ في الطابق العلوي
then came down to talk to the police, who had come in search of the body.
ثمّ نزلت للتحدث مع الشرطة التي أتت تبحث عن الجثة
You had boldly disguised yourself as the brother you murdered.
تنكّرت بمنظر أخيك الذي قتلته بكلّ جرأة
The two of you have always looked similar.
فأنتما شقيقان شبيها الملامح في الأصل
Relatives would know the difference,
،كان الأقارب ليميّزوا بينكما
but everybody else would be fooled by such a simple disguise.
لكن يمكن خداع البقية بتنكر بسيط
Then, while the police searched the house,
،بعدها، بينما أخذت الشرطة تبحث في المنزل
you jumped from the 2nd floor window to the tree, and then over the wall.
،قفزت من نافذة الطابق الثاني للشجرة ثمّ فوق الحائط
The outer side of the wall acts as an embankment,
الجانب الخارجي يؤدي دور سدّ
but there was just enough room for a single person to walk...
لكن كانت هناك مساحة كافية ليمشي شخص واحد
You then returned to the front door as the younger brother...
...رجعت بعدها للباب الأمامي بصفة الأخ الأصغر
...and acted like you had no idea what had happened!
!وتظاهرت بجهلك لما حصل
What? You found the body?
ماذا؟ وجدتم الجثة؟
Yeah!
!صحيح
The younger brother was the killer,
كان الأخ الأصغر القاتل
and the older brother who was sleeping was the corpse!
!والأخ الأكبر النائم كان الجثّة
Don't be ridiculous. He was alive.
يا للسخافة، كان حيّاً
He turned the TV off when his brother told him to,
أطفأ التلفاز عندما طلب منه شقيقه
and he even yelled at you when you broke that jar.
كما أنّه صرخ عندما حطمتم تلك الجرّة
Yes. You tried to make it look like your brother was really alive.
صحيح، حاولت جعل الأمر كما لو كان أخوك حيّاً
And you used the VCR, the answering machine,
واستعملت جهاز تسجيل الفيديو وآلة الردّ الآلي
and your cell phone to do it!
وهاتفك الخلوي لتحقيق ذلك
That shouting was something you had recorded to the answering machine
كان ذاك الصراخ تسجيلاً أرسلته لآلة الردّ الآلي
before the police showed up.
قبل وصول الشرطة
You played it back on the answering machine
شغلّته على آلة الرد باستعمال خاصية
by using your cell phone's quick-dial feature at just the right time!
الاتصال السريع لهاتفك الخلوي في الوقت المناسب
Of course, you turned off the ringers on all the phones in advance
أطفأت رنين كلّ الهواتف سلفاً بالطبع
to make it sound like your brother was yelling from upstairs.
لجعل الأمر كما لو أنّ أخاك يصرخ من الأعلى
Hey! Keep it down, will you?!
!أنتم! اخرسوا! ألا يمكنكم التزام الهدوء؟
As proof of this fact, you picked up the phone, which didn't ring,
ودليلاً لذلك، أجبت على الهاتف ،الذي لم يصدر رنيناً
when a person calling the wrong number just happened to call.
.عندما ورد اتّصال خاطئ بالصدفة
You probably saw the light on the phone blink when the phone call came.
رأيت وميض الهاتف عندما ورد الاتصال على الأرجح
If you hadn't picked it up, the answering machine would've kicked in
...لو لم تجب، كانت آلة الردّ الآلي لتستجيب
and we would have heard him yelling again...
...ونسمع ذاك الصراخ مجدداً
Yes. Like this.
أجل، هكذا
Hey! Keep it down, will you?!
!أنتم! اخرسوا! ألا يمكنكم التزام الهدوء؟
The TV turned off because you set the VCR's timer in advance
أطفئ التلفاز لأنك ضبطت مؤقت جهاز تسجيل الفيديو سلفاً
and then did a little bit of acting of your own.
ثم أكملت الأمر بتمثيلك
Isn't that right, Tanaka Tomofumi-san?
أليس ذلك صحيحاً يا تاناكا توموفومي-سان؟
Hurry! Something bad might happen to Conan-kun if you don't hurry!
!بسرعة! قد يحلّ مكروه بكونان-كن إلم تسرعوا
Give me a break, will you? I'm hanging up.
يا إلهي، هلا توقفتم؟ سأغلق الهاتف
You're one smart kid, I'll give you that.
يا لك من صبيّ حذق
That's right...
...صحيح، أنا، أنا
I killed my brother!
!قتلتُ أخي
Damn it! Where'd you go?!
!تباً! أين ذهب؟
Come back here!
!انتظر
I was being taken advantage of!
كان يستغلّني
By my worthless brother, who stayed in my house and refused to work!
،يبقى في منزلي ويرفض العمل !ذاك الأخ عديم النفع
I found these documents in your room, Tomofumi...
...وجدتُ هذه الوثائق في غرفتك يا توموفومي
These are illegally-traded stocks, yes?
إنّها أوراق مالية متداولة مخالفة للنظام، صحيح؟
Don't worry. We're brothers. I won't tell anyone.
لا تقلق، نحن أخوان فلن أفضحك
But in return, you'll take care of me for the rest of my life, right?
لكن في المقابل، ستعتني بي لبقيّة حياتي، صحيح؟
I took care of him ever since...
...اعتنيتُ به مذ آنذاك
But then he demanded even more money from me!
!لكنه أصبح يطالب بمال أكثر مني
So I bashed that parasite's head in!
!لذا سحقتُ رأس ذاك الطفيليّ
Little brat! There's no way for you to understand how I felt!
أيّها الشقي الصغير! من المستحيل !أن تفهم مشاعري
I loved my brother more than anyone else!
أحببتُ أخي أكثر من أيّ أحد
My talented brother, who was prized as a rising new novelist!
أخي غزير الموهبة الذي كوفئ !كروائي صاعد جديد
He's disguised as his older brother! He's really gone insane!
!تنكّر كأخيه الأكبر! إنه يفقد صوابه حقاً
I idolized my brother...
...كان أخي مثلي الأعلى
I always wanted to be like him...
...لطالما أردتُ أن أصبح مثله
But then he fell from grace!
!لكنّه ضاعَ وتاه
The brother I idolized so much had become a common leech!
!الأخ الذي وضعته مثالاً لي أصبح مجرّد طفيليّ
I'm taking back that brother who I looked up to!
!سأستعيد الأخ الذي تطلّعت له
Now do you get it? I'm... I'm...
...أتفهم؟ أنا... أنا
...going to become my brother!
!سأصبح أخي...
Now I'm mad!
!غضبتُ الآن
I'll use these Power Kick Shoes to finish this!
!سأستعمل حذاء مضاعفة قوّة الركل هذا لحسم الأمر
Oh no! My kicks are so strong that they destroy these vegetables!
!كلا! ركلاتي قويّة جداً بحيث تفتت الخضروات
Isn't there anything else?!
ألا يوجد شيءٌ آخر؟
Now that you've seen through my trick, I can't let you live!
لا يمكنني تركك حيّاً بعدما كشفت حيلتي
Sorry, kid! Time to die!
!آسف يا فتى، لكنك ستموت
The authorities arrived shortly afterward.
وصلت الشرطة بعد ذلك بفترة قصيرة
The inspector's faith in us was restored once more,
ورجعت ثقة المفتش بنا
and the case that started as a "missing cat" investigation came to an end.
وحُلّت القضيّة التي بدأت بالبحث عن قطّة
And then...
...ثمّ
No clients as usual...
...لا عملاء كالمعتاد
Dang, not even catching a murderer seems to have helped...
...تبّاً، حتى الإمساك بمجرم لم يساعد
Um...
المعذرة
My cat disappeared again...
...اختفت قطّتي مجدداً
I think this may be tied to another incident!
قد يكون هذا مرتبطاً بحادثة أخرى
Yeah, that's no ordinary cat, you know!
أجل، فتلك ليست قطّةً عادية
Come on! Let's take the case!
!لنقبل بها
Yeah! Besides, we have nothing else to do!
أجل، فلا شيء لدينا لنفعله
We found out later that Hiroki's cat Akira was nothing more
،اتّضح لاحقاً أنّ قطّة هيروكي، أكيرا لم تكن سوى مجرّد قطّة مشاغبة
than a mischievous cat who liked to sneak into all kinds of places.
تحب التسلل لمختلف الأماكن
She never led us to any further incidents.
ولم تقدنا لأيّ قضايا أخرى
Your husband was into swordsmanship, I take it?
كان زوجك سيّافاً، أليس كذلك؟
Which means that the killer was quite an expert as well...
مما يعني أنّ القاتل كان سيّافاً بارعاً بدوره
None of the three callers have alibis!
لا يملك أيّ من الزوّار الثلاثة حجّة غياب
You're confessing that you, yourself, are the murderer!
!اعترفت بأنّك القاتل في رسالتك
On the next Conan--
في الحلقة القادمة من كونان
The Antique Collector Murder.
جريمة قتل جامع الآثار
Next Conan's Hint:
تلميح الحلقة القادمة
Scratches on a dresser
خدوش على خزانة